{
    "id": "9d05096fd2364b768567529df78a5070",
    "title": "Do or Make",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "35834ad2c46c4062acf225d1b404b66c",
            "title": "Do or Make",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "Has he agreed to ………………….. the work?",
                    "description": "Do can mean execute or carry out.",
                    "answers": [
                        "do",
                        "make",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "Have you ……………………….. what I told you?",
                    "description": "Do can mean finish or complete.",
                    "answers": [
                        "made",
                        "done",
                        "did"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "The company …………………….. bicycles and tricycles.",
                    "description": "To make is to produce or manufacture.",
                    "answers": [
                        "makes",
                        "does",
                        "make"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "Why are you always ………………………. trouble?",
                    "description": "We say make trouble. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "making",
                        "doing",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "Will this tablecloth ……………………. or should I use another?",
                    "description": "Do can mean suffice or be good enough.",
                    "answers": [
                        "do",
                        "make",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "He ……………………. a speech on the occasion.",
                    "description": "To make a speech is to deliver a speech.",
                    "answers": [
                        "made",
                        "did",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "They …………………… the kitchen and the bathrooms every day.",
                    "description": "To do the kitchen is to clean it.",
                    "answers": [
                        "do",
                        "make",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "I won’t go and you can’t ……………………… me.",
                    "description": "To make someone go is to compel them to go.",
                    "answers": [
                        "do",
                        "done",
                        "make"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "Laws are …………………… to be obeyed.",
                    "description": "To make laws is to enact them.",
                    "answers": [
                        "made",
                        "did",
                        "done"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "Last summer we ……………………. ten countries in one month.",
                    "description": "To do ten countries is to travel through ten countries.",
                    "answers": [
                        "did",
                        "done",
                        "made"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "Hurry or we won’t …………………… the train.",
                    "description": "To make the train is to catch it.",
                    "answers": [
                        "do",
                        "done",
                        "make"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "When buying a bag, look closely at its ....................................",
                    "description": "Make can mean brand.",
                    "answers": [
                        "do",
                        "make",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}